<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FieldReferences on Tech Writing Demo</title><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/</link><description>Recent content in FieldReferences on Tech Writing Demo</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/apiconnection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/apiconnection/</guid><description>ApiConnection Connections contains authentication and other information required by NetMatix in order log into external services through their Application Program Interface (API) endpoints to access data stored in those services.
Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Api Connection Id ApiConnectionId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Name ApiConnectionName String [Descriptor] The name of the external service you want to set up a connection for. Description ApiConnectionDescription String [Template: MultilineText] Use the Connection Description property to describe the Connection in more detail and provide guidance to other users.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/appevent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/appevent/</guid><description>AppEvent View the App Event history
Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Event Id EventId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Topic EventTopic String [Descriptor] [MaxLen: 40] A Topic is used to group AppEvent messages of the same type. The Topic for AppEvents raised by changes to entities, eg Contacts, will always be the same as the entity name. Subtopic SubTopic String The SubTopic is used to further specify the type of the AppEvent message.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/applicationuser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/applicationuser/</guid><description>ApplicationUser Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Id Id String [Key] [Required] [Unique] [MaxLen: 36] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] User Name UserName String [Descriptor] Normalized User Name NormalizedUserName String Email Email String Normalized Email NormalizedEmail String Email Confirmed EmailConfirmed Bool Password Hash PasswordHash String Security Stamp SecurityStamp String Concurrency Stamp ConcurrencyStamp String Phone Number PhoneNumber String Phone Number Confirmed PhoneNumberConfirmed Bool Two Factor Enabled TwoFactorEnabled Bool Lockout End LockoutEnd DateTimeOffset? Lockout Enabled LockoutEnabled Bool Access Failed Count AccessFailedCount Int</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/auditevent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/auditevent/</guid><description>AuditEvent Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Audit Event Id AuditEventId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Audit Event Type AuditEventType AuditEventType Added/Updated/Deleted/Assigned/Retracted Allowable Values: RecordAdded RecordUpdated RecordDeleted RecordArchived RecordUnarchived OwnershipAssigned OwnershipUnassigned OwnershipDelegated WatcherAdded WatcherRemoved StatusUpdate LoginRemoved Opened Closed StatusUpdate LoginRemoved RelatedAccountLoginAdded RelatedAccountLoginRemoved RelationshipAdded RelationshipModified RelationshipRemoved IsBillingContactAssigned IsBillingContactUnassigned IsPrimaryContactAssigned IsPrimaryContactUnassigned RecordActivated RecordDeactivated Audit Event Date AuditEventDate DateTime Date and time the event took place Entity Name EntityName String [Descriptor] [MaxLen: 40] Name of the entity the event applies to, eg Client or Portfolio Model Name ModelName String [MaxLen: 60] Model name if applicable, eg ClientEditModel.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/country/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/country/</guid><description>Country Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Country Code CountryCode String [Key] [Required] [Unique] [MinLen: 2] [MaxLen: 2] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] ISO 2 letter country code. Country Name CountryName String [Required] [Descriptor] ISO 3 Letter Code Iso3Code String [Unique] [MaxLen: 3] ISO 3 letter country code. Currency Code CurrencyCode String [ForeignKey Currency] [MaxLen: 3] Address Template AddressTemplate String Base List BaseList Bool</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/currency/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/currency/</guid><description>Currency Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Currency Code CurrencyCode String [Key] [Required] [Unique] [MinLen: 3] [MaxLen: 3] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] Currency Name CurrencyDescription String [Required] [Descriptor]</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/currencypair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/currencypair/</guid><description>CurrencyPair Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Currency Pair Id CurrencyPairId Int [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Base Currency Code BaseCurrencyCode String [ForeignKey Currency] [Descriptor] [MaxLen: 3] Quote Currency Code QuoteCurrencyCode String [ForeignKey Currency] [MaxLen: 3] Data Source DataSource String Data Set DataSet String</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/currencyrate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/currencyrate/</guid><description>CurrencyRate Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Currency Rate Id CurrencyRateId Int [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Currency Pair Id CurrencyPairId Int [ForeignKey CurrencyPair] [Required] Rate Date RateDate DateTime Rate Value RateValue Decimal</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/job/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/job/</guid><description>Job Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Job Id JobId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Hangfire Job Id HangfireJobId String Hangfire Job Active HangfireJobActive Bool Job JobDescription String [Required] [Descriptor] [Unique] Task Name JobMethodCall String Provide the name of a class with the IBackgroundTask interface. Schedule ScheduleType ScheduleType Allowable Values: None Hourly Daily Weekly Monthly Minutes RunOnce Description ScheduleDescription String Minute Interval MinuteInterval MinuteInterval Allowable Values: Minute01 Minute02 Minute03 Minute04 Minute05 Minute10 Minute15 Minute20 Minute25 Minute30 Minute35 Minute40 Minute45 Minute50 Minute55 Hour Interval HourInterval HourInterval Allowable Values: Hour01 Hour02 Hour03 Hour04 Hour05 Hour06 Hour07 Hour08 Hour09 Hour10 Hour11 Hour12 Minute Offset MinuteOffset MinuteOffset Allowable Values: Offset01 Offset02 Offset03 Offset04 Offset05 Offset10 Offset15 Offset20 Offset25 Offset30 Offset35 Offset40 Offset45 Offset50 Offset55 Day Of Month DayOfMonth DayOfMonth Allowable Values: Day01 Day02 Day03 Day04 Day05 Day06 Day07 Day08 Day09 Day10 Day11 Day12 Day13 Day14 Day15 Day16 Day17 Day18 Day19 Day20 Day21 Day22 Day23 Day24 Day25 Day26 Day27 Day28 Start Time StartTime TimeSpan Time Zone TimeZoneId TimeZoneIds Allowable Values: MoroccoStandardTime GMTStandardTime GreenwichStandardTime WEuropeStandardTime CentralEuropeStandardTime RomanceStandardTime CentralEuropeanStandardTime WCentralAfricaStandardTime JordanStandardTime GTBStandardTime MiddleEastStandardTime EgyptStandardTime SouthAfricaStandardTime FLEStandardTime IsraelStandardTime EEuropeStandardTime NamibiaStandardTime ArabicStandardTime ArabStandardTime RussianStandardTime EAfricaStandardTime GeorgianStandardTime IranStandardTime ArabianStandardTime AzerbaijanStandardTime MauritiusStandardTime CaucasusStandardTime AfghanistanStandardTime EkaterinburgStandardTime PakistanStandardTime WestAsiaStandardTime IndiaStandardTime SriLankaStandardTime NepalStandardTime NCentralAsiaStandardTime CentralAsiaStandardTime MyanmarStandardTime SEAsiaStandardTime NorthAsiaStandardTime ChinaStandardTime NorthAsiaEastStandardTime SingaporeStandardTime WAustraliaStandardTime TaipeiStandardTime TokyoStandardTime KoreaStandardTime YakutskStandardTime CenAustraliaStandardTime AUSCentralStandardTime EAustraliaStandardTime AUSEasternStandardTime WestPacificStandardTime TasmaniaStandardTime VladivostokStandardTime CentralPacificStandardTime NewZealandStandardTime FijiStandardTime TongaStandardTime AzoresStandardTime CapeVerdeStandardTime MidAtlanticStandardTime ESouthAmericaStandardTime ArgentinaStandardTime SAEasternStandardTime GreenlandStandardTime MontevideoStandardTime NewfoundlandStandardTime AtlanticStandardTime SAWesternStandardTime CentralBrazilianStandardTime PacificSAStandardTime VenezuelaStandardTime SAPacificStandardTime EasternStandardTime USEasternStandardTime CentralAmericaStandardTime CentralStandardTime CentralStandardTimeMexico CanadaCentralStandardTime USMountainStandardTime MountainStandardTimeMexico MountainStandardTime PacificStandardTime PacificStandardTimeMexico AlaskanStandardTime HawaiianStandardTime SamoaStandardTime DatelineStandardTime Time Zone Iana Name TimeZoneIanaName String UTC Offset TimeZoneUtcOffset Decimal Timezone offset in hours relative to UTC (GMT).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/jobstatus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/jobstatus/</guid><description>JobStatus Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Job Status Id JobStatusId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Job Name JobName String [Descriptor] Job Messages JobMessages String Job State JobState JobState Allowable Values: NotStarted Running CompletedSuccessfully CompletedWithError CancellationRequested CancelledByUser Percent Complete PercentComplete Int? Sub Job Description SubJobDescription String Run Summary RunSummary String Start Time StartTime DateTime? End Time EndTime DateTime? Elapsed Time ElapsedTime TimeSpan? Hangfire Job Id HangfireJobId String User Id UserId String Developer Info DeveloperInfo String Organization Id OrganizationId Guid?</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/listviewdefinition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/listviewdefinition/</guid><description>ListViewDefinition Define and manage list views to see a specific set of Clients, Leads or other entity records.
Field Label Field Name Field Type Description List View Definition Id ListViewDefinitionId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Entity Id EntityId Guid? [ForeignKey MetaEntity] Parent List View Id ParentListViewId Guid? Organization Id OrganizationId Guid? [ForeignKey Organization] User Id UserId String [ForeignKey ApplicationUser] List Type ListType ListType The list type determines whether the list as presented in tabular format or as a form per row.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/media/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/media/</guid><description>Media The Media entity stores links to media such as PDFs, images, and spreadsheets uploaded by employees or clients. It is a system table and cannot be edited by users.
Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Media Id MediaId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Blob Name BlobName String Media such as images, documents and other files are stored as BLOBs (Binary Large Objects) in Azure Cloud Storage. File Name FileName String [Descriptor] Original name of the uploaded media file.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metaapp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metaapp/</guid><description>MetaApp Configure applications, related entities, pages and profiles
Field Label Field Name Field Type Description App Id AppId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] App Name AppName String [Required] [Descriptor] The name of the App as it appears on pages and forms App API Name AppApiName String [Required] [TenantUnique] [MinLen: 2] [MaxLen: 50] [Regex: ^[a-zA-Z_][a-zA-Z0-9_.-]*$] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] A unique and url-safe API name for this app. It is used to refer to the app and in internal processes and in the external API.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metaappmetaentitylink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metaappmetaentitylink/</guid><description>MetaAppMetaEntityLink Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Link Id LinkId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] App Id AppId Guid [ForeignKey MetaApp] [Required] Entity Id EntityId Guid [ForeignKey MetaEntity] [Required] Display In Menu DisplayInMenu Bool Display In Launcher DisplayInLauncher Bool Custom IsCustom Bool Display Order DisplayOrder Int Organization Id OrganizationId Guid? [ForeignKey Organization] Created Date CreatedDate DateTime Created By CreatedBy String [Descriptor] Modified Date ModifiedDate DateTime Modified By ModifiedBy String Row Version RowVersion Int</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metaappuserprofilelink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metaappuserprofilelink/</guid><description>MetaAppUserProfileLink Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Link Id LinkId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] App Id AppId Guid [ForeignKey MetaApp] [Required] Profile Id ProfileId Guid [ForeignKey UserProfile] [Required] Visible IsVisible Bool Determines whether an App is visible for users with this profile. Note: This checkbox does not grant access to the app&amp;rsquo;s entities or fields. Access security for these items must be set in User Profiles. Default IsDefault Bool The Default checkbox specifies which app should be started automatically when users with this profile log in.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metacommand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metacommand/</guid><description>MetaCommand Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Command Id CommandId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Entity Id EntityId Guid? [ForeignKey MetaEntity] App Id AppId Guid? [ForeignKey MetaApp] Command Name CommandName String [Required] [Descriptor] The name of the Command as it appears on pages and forms Command API Name CommandApiName String [Required] [TenantUnique] [MinLen: 2] [MaxLen: 50] [Regex: ^[a-zA-Z_][a-zA-Z0-9_.-]*$] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] A unique and url-safe API name for this command. It is used to refer to the command in processes and in the external API.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metaentity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metaentity/</guid><description>##MetaEntity Capture your unique firm data in custom fields or in new custom entities
Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Entity Id EntityId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Entity Name EntityName String [Required] [Descriptor] The name of the entity as it appears on pages and forms. Plural Name PluralEntityName String The plural name of the entity. This label is used as the title in list headings. Short Entity Name ShortEntityName String Used in column headings and other places where the full name would not fit.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metafield/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metafield/</guid><description>MetaField Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Field Id FieldId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Field Name FieldName String [Descriptor] The field name is what you an your users see throughout the interface. Field API Name FieldApiName String [Required] [Descriptor] [Unique] [MinLen: 2] [MaxLen: 50] [Regex: ^[a-zA-Z_][a-zA-Z0-9_.-]*$] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] A unique and url-safe API name for this field. It is used to refer to the field in processes and in the external API.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metaform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metaform/</guid><description>MetaForm Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Form Id FormId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Entity Id EntityId Guid [ForeignKey MetaEntity] [Required] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] Name FormName String [Required] [Descriptor] The name of the Form as it appears on pages and forms Entity Name EntityName String [ReadOnly] The name of the entity linked to this form. The list of potential fields are derived from this entity and those linked toit with lookup relationships.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metalist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metalist/</guid><description>MetaList Configure how lists of entities are displayed
Field Label Field Name Field Type Description List Id ListId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Entity Id EntityId Guid [ForeignKey MetaEntity] [Required] List API Name ListApiName String [Required] [TenantUnique] [MinLen: 2] [MaxLen: 50] [Regex: ^[a-zA-Z_][a-zA-Z0-9_.-]*$] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] A unique and url-safe API name for this list. It is used to refer to the list in processes and in the external API. The name is derived from the list label by default and can only be edited when creating a new list.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metapage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metapage/</guid><description>MetaPage Configure how entity lists and details pages are displayed
Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Page Id PageId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Entity Id EntityId Guid [ForeignKey MetaEntity] [Required] Name PageName String [Required] [Descriptor] The name of the Page as it appears on pages and forms Page API Name PageApiName String [Required] [TenantUnique] [MinLen: 2] [MaxLen: 50] [Regex: ^[a-zA-Z_][a-zA-Z0-9_.-]*$] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] A unique and url-safe API name for this page.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metapagetemplate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metapagetemplate/</guid><description>MetaPageTemplate Configure templates used when creating new pages
Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Template Id TemplateId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Name TemplateName String [Required] [Descriptor] The name of the Template as it appears on pages and forms Page Template API Name TemplateApiName String [Required] [TenantUnique] [MinLen: 2] [MaxLen: 50] [Regex: ^[a-zA-Z_][a-zA-Z0-9_.-]*$] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] A unique and url-safe API name for this page template. It is used to refer to the template in processes and in the external API.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metapageuserprofilelink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metapageuserprofilelink/</guid><description>MetaPageUserProfileLink Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Link Id LinkId Int [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Page Id PageId Guid [ForeignKey MetaPage] [Required] Profile Id ProfileId Guid [ForeignKey UserProfile] [Required] Default IsDefaultForProfile Bool When multiple pages have been linked to the same User Profile, then this field can be used to indicate which page should appear by default. If no default has been set, then the first page will appear based on its name in alphabetical order.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metareport/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/metareport/</guid><description>MetaReport Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Report Id ReportId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Entity Id EntityId Guid [ForeignKey MetaEntity] [Required] Name ReportName String [Required] [Descriptor] The name of the Report as it appears on pages and forms Report API Name ReportApiName String [Required] [TenantUnique] [MinLen: 2] [MaxLen: 50] [Regex: ^[a-zA-Z_][a-zA-Z0-9_.-]*$] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] A unique and url-safe API name for this report. It is used to refer to the report in processes and in the external API.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/picklist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/picklist/</guid><description>Picklist Modify user-defined picklists, eg Client Categories or Marketing Segments
Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Picklist Id PicklistId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Picklist Name PicklistName String [Descriptor] [Unique] [MinLen: 2] [MaxLen: 50] [Regex: ^[a-zA-Z_]\w*$] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] A unique and url-safe name for this picklist. It is used to refer to the picklist in processes and in the external API. The name is derived from the picklist label by default and can only be edited when creating a new picklist.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/picklistitem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/picklistitem/</guid><description>PicklistItem Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Picklist Item Id PicklistItemId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Item Name PicklistItemName String [Descriptor] [MinLen: 2] [MaxLen: 100] [Regex: ^[\w_-&amp;amp;/.,&amp;rsquo;:&amp;lt;&amp;gt;+%()$ۣ ]*$] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] Once created, picklist items can only be renamed with the Rename menu option. Picklist Id PicklistId Guid [ForeignKey Picklist] [Required] Picklist Name PicklistName String [MaxLen: 50] [ReadOnly] The name of the picklist this item is a member of. Help Text HelpText String Admins can add additional information for their users on a picklist item here and include guidance on the correct use of picklist items.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/staff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/staff/</guid><description>Staff Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Staff Id StaffId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] User Id UserId String [ForeignKey ApplicationUser] User Profile ProfileId Guid [ForeignKey UserProfile] [Required] First Name FirstName String Last Name LastName String Staff Name StaffName String [Descriptor] Notes StaffNotes String Image MediaId Guid? [ForeignKey Media] [Template: Image] LinkedIn LinkedInPage String [Template: Url] Facebook FacebookPage String [Template: Url] Telephone Telephone1 String [Template: Telephone] Secondary Telephone Telephone2 String [Template: Telephone] Email Email1 String [Template: Email] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] This email address is used to log into the system.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/systemsetting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/systemsetting/</guid><description>SystemSetting Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Key Name KeyName String [Key] [Required] [Descriptor] [Unique] [MaxLen: 256] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] Key Value KeyValue String</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/translation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/translation/</guid><description>Translation Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Translation Id TranslationId Int [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] String Id StringId String [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] English StringEnGb String String En Gb Verified StringEnGbVerified Bool Dutch StringNlNl String Verified? StringNlNlVerified Bool German StringDeDe String Verified? StringDeDeVerified Bool French StringFrFr String Verified? StringFrFrVerified Bool Orphan String OrphanString Bool Organization Id OrganizationId Guid? [ForeignKey Organization] Created Date CreatedDate DateTime Created By CreatedBy String [Descriptor] Modified Date ModifiedDate DateTime Modified By ModifiedBy String Row Version RowVersion Int</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/userprofile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/userprofile/</guid><description>UserProfile Configure access permissions for each user profile
Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Profile Id ProfileId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Profile Name ProfileName String [Required] [Descriptor] User access security profile name Profile Description ProfileDescription String User Type UserType UserType [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] Allowable Values: Anonymous Contact Employee TenantApiToken TenantAgent Staff System View All Data CanViewAllData Bool Enable for users who need access to all of a firm&amp;rsquo;s data but do not need to modify it.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/userprofileitem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bhaskarndas.github.io/techwriting/fieldreference/userprofileitem/</guid><description>UserProfileItem Field Label Field Name Field Type Description Profile Item Id ProfileItemId Guid [Key] [Required] [ReadOnly] Profile Id ProfileId Guid [ForeignKey UserProfile] [Required] Name ProfileItemName String [Required] [Descriptor] [ReadOnlyAfterInsert] Security Profile Name Description ProfileItemDescription String Scope Id ScopeId String Scope Ids are identifiers for resources that a user wants to access. The resource can be an entity together with related tables (eg Securities including EOD Prices), an operation (eg, &amp;lsquo;Import EOD Security Prices&amp;rsquo;) or a combination of both (eg, &amp;lsquo;Manage Portfolios&amp;rsquo;).</description></item></channel></rss>